{
    "id": "195fba8abb7b45629c6cc4ea08b08f01",
    "title": "Auxiliary Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Help! He ……………………………… be drowned, if no one saves him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "shall",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "79de896d451b48a1a8385e026f2a011f"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………………. I send an application?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Will",
                "Would",
                "Should"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "52d642b5aa4340eabe2ed49fd4652bfc"
        },
        {
            "question": "Pay your fees in time lest you ………………………………. be fined.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shall",
                "should",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "37a4e5286680411e8d87ba60bb347da2"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I were you, I ……………………………….. do it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wouldn't",
                "can't",
                "won't"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a5fd04b7938a4ebe95044d1a18605720"
        },
        {
            "question": "That ………………………….. have been a shooting star.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must",
                "can",
                "shall"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9ccd8c02166e4472b002c69d66b7952b"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………….. you like to go to the pictures tonight?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Would",
                "Should",
                "May"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0e10af61b2154122a1508447e8ea8cbd"
        },
        {
            "question": "I think it ……………………………… rain tonight.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "shall"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e59cc01b056849f9aeeb79b43d232604"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. I wait any longer?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Should",
                "Would",
                "Will"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "93b15a4681554816a52c414b8760fda7"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………………… you be able to visit us tomorrow?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Will",
                "Should",
                "Can"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "21b7336878404e9986d6cffae219ca85"
        },
        {
            "question": "In my younger days I ………………………………. run four miles at a stretch.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "could",
                "can",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9d795b8e3fee40ada4cb1439771dbb81"
        }
    ]
}